pets4you.com 2013-05-17

# Privacy Policy - Pets4You.com

#### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

#### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

• To personalize your experience  
(Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.)

• To improve our website  
(We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.)

• To improve customer service  
(Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.)

• To process transactions

(Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.)

• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

• To send periodic emails

> The email address you provide (for order processing) will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to stop receiving our emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of every email.

#### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.  

#### Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow such transfers) that enables the site's or service provider's system to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, to better understand and honor your preferences during future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and user interactions so that we can offer better site experiences anduser  tools in the future.

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to any outside parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  

#### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these third-party sites and your experiences.  

#### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.

#### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act): we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years of age or older.  

#### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.  

#### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section which establish the operation, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.pets4you.com/terms.html>  

#### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to this Privacy Policy  

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.  

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

**Address:** P.O. Box 948,  Tucson, AZ 85702 USA  
**Telephone:** (520) 623-4365  
**Website:** <http://www.pets4you.com/>  
**Email:** [customers@pets4you.com](mailto:customers@pets4you.com)
